National Railroad Adjustment Board Case Files 5837
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- N.R.A.B. First Division Award Books Volumes 149 to 168 Last Volume (Box 7)
  - Award No. 967. Docket No. 935. Saint-Louis-San Francisco. Campbell Claims., 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Award No. 976. Docket No. 972. Southern Railway. Ashville, North Carolina. Time Last Rest Day., 1954 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- N.R.A.B. Second Division Award Books Volumes 1 to 27 (Box 8)
  - Docket No. 536. Award No. 568. Pennsylvania Railroad. South Street Yard, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Docket No. 537. Award No. 569. Pennsylvania Railroad. Dock Street Yard, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania., 1948-1949 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Docket No. 538. Award No. 570. Pennsylvania Railroad. Morris Street Yard, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Docket No. 539. Award No. 571. Pennsylvania Railroad. Midvale Yard, Philadelphia Terminal Division, Philadelphia, Philadelphia., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Docket No. 561. Award No. 575. Pennsylvania Railroad. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Docket No. 567. Award No. 576. Pennsylvania Railroad. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Docket No. 591. Award No. 577. Milwaukee Road., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Docket No. 592. Award No. 578. Milwaukee Road, Bensenville, Illinois., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Docket No. 576. Award No. 580. Milwaukee Road, Green Bay, Wisconsin., 1948-1949 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Docket No. 571. Award No. 594. TRRA., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Docket No. 573. Award No. 595. Pennsylvania Railroad., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Docket No. 575. Award No. 596. Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line Railroad Co., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Docket No. 577. Award No. 597. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. Attending Meeting., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Docket No. 578. Award No. 598. Spokane, Portland and Settle Railroad Co. Portland, Oregon., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Docket No. 584. Award No. 600. Seaboard Air Line. Bainbridge, Georgia., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Docket No. 584. Award No. 600. Seaboard Air Line., 1951-1954 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Docket No. 584. Award No. 602. Santa Fe. Frank Smith. Chicago, Illinois., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Docket No. 590. Award No. 603. Santa Fe., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Docket No. 613. Award No. 605. Wabash Railroad. Detroit Terminal., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Docket No. 586. Award No. 606. Pennsylvania Railroad. Williamsport Division., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Docket No. 605. Award No. 609. Chicago Great Western. Chicago, Illinois., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Docket No. 606. Award No. 610. Chicago Great Western. ER Frank. Chicago, Illinois., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Docket No. 608. Award No. 611. Pennsylvania railroad. Fort Wayne, Indiana., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Docket No. 610. Award No. 612. Milwaukee Road. A.E. Maloney., 1960 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Docket No. 628. Award No. 613. Chicago, Burlington and Quincy. North St. Louis, Missouri., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Docket No. 629. Award No. 614. Chicago, Burlington and Quincy. CL Burns. North Saint Louis, Missouri., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Docket No. 630. Award No. 615. Chicago, Burlington and Quincy. VD Kamp. North Saint Louis, Missouri., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Docket No. 631. Award No. 616. Chicago, Burlington and Quincy. East St. Louis, Illinois., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Docket No. 632. Award No. 617. Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad. LE Reames. East St. Louis, Illinois., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Docket No. 633. Award No. 618. Chicago, Burlington and Quincy. East St. Louis, Illinois., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Docket No. 634. Award No. 619. Chicago, Burlington and Quincy. North St. Louis., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Alphabetical Lists of Railroad. New York Central Documents., 1943-1959 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Docket No. 612. Award No. 621. Santa Fe., 1949-1951 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Docket No. 611. Award No. 620. Santa Fe., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Docket No. 616. Award No. 623. Northern Pacific. Centralia Yard., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Northern Pacific. Centralia Yard. Docket No. 616., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Docket No. 617. Award No. 624. Northern Pacific. Pasco Yard., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Docket No. 642. Award No. 625. Union Pacific Railroad. Idaho Falls, Idaho., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Docket No. 649. Award No. 627. South Buffalo., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Docket No. 654. Award No. 628. Santa Fe., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Docket No. 655. Award No. 629. Santa Fe. Brooks Eastman. Bakersfield, California., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Docket No. 656. Award No. 630. Santa Fe., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Docket No. 651. Award No. 631. Santa Fe, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Docket No. 658. Award No. 632. Santa Fe Grievances., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Docket No. 659. Award No. 633. Santa Fe. San Angels, Texas., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Docket No. 660. Award No. 634. Santa Fe., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Docket No. 661. Award No. 635. Santa Fe. Argentine Yard., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- N.R.A.B. Second Division Award Books Volumes 28 to 50 (Box 9)
  - Award No. 2547. Docket No. 2571. Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul., 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 2553. Docket No. 2525. Lehigh Valley. One and a half rate., 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 2556. Docket No. 2555. Seaboard Coastline. Vacation Pay., 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 2557. Docket No. 2556. Norfolk and Western., 1970 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 2558. Docket No. 2589. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. One Day's Pay., 1970 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 2559. Docket No. 2591. Penn Central Co. System Docket 298. Buffalo Division Case Bd-36., 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 2563. Docket No. 2546. Louisville and Nashville Railroad Co. One and a Half Day's Pay., 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 2564. Docket No. 2530. Central Railroad of New Jersey., 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 2565. Docket No. 2532. The Penn Central Co. RYA System Docket 297. Pittsburgh Division Case No. YM-9-69., 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Award No. 2567. Docket No. 2544. Lehigh Valley., 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Award No. 2568. Docket No. 2545. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad., 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 2569. Docket No. 2553. Chicago, Milwaukee., 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Award No. 2571. Docket No. 2565. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific., 1970 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Award No. 2572. Docket No. 2566. Norfolk and Western., 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Award No. 2573. Docket No. 2567. Norfolk and Western. Deferred Suspension., 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Award No. 2574. Docket No. 2570. Norfolk and Western. James R. David., 1970 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Award No. 2576. Docket No. 2577. Missouri-Kansas-Texas. Reinstatement., 1971 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Award No. 2579. Docket No. 2476. Chicago and North Western Railway Co., 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Award No. 2580. Docket No. 2477. Missouri-Kansas-Texas. Suspension., 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Award No. 2582. Docket No. 2490. Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis., 1967-1970 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Award No. 2592. Docket No. 2610. Norfolk and Western., 1970 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Award No. 2588. Docket No. 2552. Chicago, Milwaukee. One and a Half Time Pay., 1970 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Award No. 2589. Docket No. 2560. Chicago and North Western. Time and a Half Pay., 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Award No. 2595. Docket No. 2563. Penn Central Co. Central Region. System Docket307. Pittsburgh Division Case YM-8-69., 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Award No. 2596. Docket No. 2582. Missouri Pacific. A Day's Pay., 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Award No. 2597. Docket No. 2580. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad. One Day's Pay., 1970 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Port Terminal Exhibits. Presented but not Produced., 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Award No. 2602. Docket No. 2451. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie. One and a Half Time., 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- N.R.A.B. Second Division Award Books Volumes 51 to 68 Last Volume (Box 10)
  - Award No. 2489. Docket No. 2500. Denver, Rio Grand Railroad. One Day's Pay., 1969 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 2490. Docket No. 2505. Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad., 1969 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 2491. Docket No. 2506. Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad., 1969 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 2493. Docket No. 2503. Lake Front Dock and Terminal Company., 1952-1969 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 2494. Docket No. 2504. Chicago and North Western Railway. Van Landschoot., 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Killing of Alphonse van Landschoot., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 2498. Docket No. 2522. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad., 1969 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 2502. Docket No. 2507. Norfolk and Western., 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 2503. Docket No. 2508. Norfolk and Western., 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Award No. 2504. Docket No. 2492. Jacksonville Terminal., 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Award No. 2509. Docket No. 2551. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad., 1969 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 2520. Docket No. 2494. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Co., 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Award No. 2521. Docket No. 2502. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad., 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Award No. 2522. Docket No. 2577. Long Island Railroad., 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Award No. 2523. Docket No. 2518. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railroad., 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Award No. 2525. Docket No. 2529. Soo Line Railroad., 1970 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Award No. 2532. Docket No. 2469. Penn Central., 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Award No. 2533. Docket No. 2470. Grand Trunk Western., 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Award No. 2534. Docket No. 2472. Union Belt of Detroit., 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Award No. 2539. Docket No. 2452. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific., 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Switch Lists, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Award No. 2540. Docket No. 2454. Texas and Pacific, Missouri-Pacific Terminal Railroad of New Orleans., 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Award No. 2541. Docket No. 2457. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe., 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Award No. 2542. Docket No. 2459. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co., 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Award No. 2543. Docket No. 2531. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific., 1970 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Award No. 2545. Docket No. 2564. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific., 1969 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Award No. 2546. Docket No. 2569. Penn Central Co., 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- RYA Magazine "The Railroad Yardmaster" 1925 to 1944 (Box 11)
  - Docket No. 833. Award No. 839. The Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Co., 1952 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Docket No. 836. Award No. 842. Minneapolis and St. Louis Railway. Claim., 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Docket No. 837. Award No. 843. Delaware and Hudson Railroad. Black Case., 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Docket No. 840. Award No. 844. Nashville Terminals, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Docket No. 846. Award No. 850. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. Paul Haines., 1952 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Docket No. 847. Award No. 851. Baltimore and Ohio. McCormick., 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Docket No. 851. Award No. 852. Elgin, Joliet and Eastern Railway., 1952 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Docket No. 869. Award No. 853. Delaware and Hudson., 1952 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Docket No. 854. Award No. 861. Great Northern Railway Co. Casey., 1952 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Docket No. 859. Award No. 863. Kentucky and Indiana Terminal Railroad. Stuard and French., 1952 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Docket No. 860. Award No. 864. Kentucky and Indiana Terminal Railroad Co. Louisville, Kentucky., 1951 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Docket No. 864. Award No. 870. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad Co. Herington, Kansas., 1953 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Docket No. 865. Award No. 871. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad Co., 1952-1954 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Docket No. 870. Award No. 874. Kentucky and Indiana Terminal Railroad Co. Hughes., 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Docket No. 906. Award No. 877. The Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Co. Gray's Yard., 1953 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Docket No. 876. Award No. 884. Baltimore and Ohio. Quinn., 1953 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Docket No. 877. Award No. 885. Grand Trunk Western Railroad. Howie and Graves, et al., 1951-1953 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Docket No. 879. Award No. 886. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. Power., 1953 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Docket No. 891. Award No. 895. Lehigh Valley Railroad Co. Dougherty., 1953 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Docket No. 893. Award No. 897. Seaboard Air Line. Bizzell and Smith., 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Docket No. 896. Award No. 899. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Co. Robinson., 1952 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Docket No. 933. Award No. 902. Grand Trunk Western. Williams Claim., 1953 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Docket No. 910. Award No. 913. Railway Transfer of the City of Minneapolis. Brennan Case., 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Docket No. 951. Award No. 922. Northern Pacific Railway Co. Vacation Claim., 1953 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Docket No. 911. Award No. 923. Louisiana and Arkansas Railway Co. R.W. Gandy., 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- RYA Magazine "The Railroad Yardmaster" 1945-1982 Last Edition (Box 12)
  - Award No. 1897. Docket No. 1821. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co., 1961-1963 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 1898. Docket No. 1843. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe., 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 1907. Docket No. 1878. System Docket No. 76. RYA vs. Pennsylvania Railroad. Marrone Disqualification, New York Region., 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 1915. Docket No. 1896. System Docket No. 80. New York, Oscar Johnson., 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 1916. Docket No. 1897. RYA vs. Long Island Railroad., 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 1917. Docket No. 1903. RYA vs. Grand Trunk Western Railway Co., 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 1921. Docket No. 1900. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co. Patrick. San Bernardino, California., 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 1922. Docket No. 1907. System No. 85. New York Region 17/62. FJ Donigan., 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 1930. Docket No. 1939. System No. 104. Philadelphia 17080. Stiles., 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Award No. 1934. Docket No. 1901. RYA vs. Union Belt of Detroit., 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Award No. 1937. Docket No. 1913. RYA vs. Louisville and Nashville Railroad Co. Redding. New Orleans, Louisiana., 1964 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 1938. Docket No. 1917. RYA vs. Long Island Rail Road. Brennan., 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Award No. 1939. Docket No. 1918. RYA vs. Long Island Railroad. Brennan., 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Award No. 1940. Docket No. 1922. RYA vs. South Pacific Co. SA Robben., 1962-1964 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Award No. 1940. Docket No. 1922. Southern Pacific Co. SA Robben., 1962-1964 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Award No. 1942. Docket No. 1959. RYA vs. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Co., 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Award No. 1943. Docket No. 1973. No. 117. Southwestern region Meeting. Terrehaute., 1964 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Award No. 1944. Docket No. 1972. No.116. Southwestern Region Meeting., 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Award No. 1946. Docket No. 1974. No. 118. Mansfield. Haupt and Wigton., 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Award No. 1947. Docket No. 1975. No. 119. Chesapeake Region 83. Morganwick Claim. Pennsylvania Railroad., 1964 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Award No. 1950. Docket No. 1987. RYA vs. Great Northern Railway Co., 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Award No. 1963. Docket No. 1981. No. 105. Chesapeake Region No. 80. Morganwick Claim., 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Award No. 1964. Docket No. 1995. RYA vs. Erie Lackawanna Railroad Co., 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Award No. 1965. Docket No. 1968. RYA vs. Chicago and North Western Railway Co., 1964 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Award No. 1966. Docket No. 2007. RYA vs. Detroit and Toledo Shore Line Railroad Co., 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Award No. 1980. Docket No. 1948. RYA vs. Chicago and North Western Railway Co., 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 247-366 (Box 13)
  - Award No. 1850. Docket No. 1824. RYA vs. Pennsylvania Railroad Co. Brann., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 1857. Docket No. 1828. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. Kansas City, Kansas., 1961-1963 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 1858. Docket No. 1829. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. Kansas City, Kansas., 1963 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 1859. Docket No. 1830. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. Kansas City, Kansas., 1961-1963 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 1860. Docket No. 1831. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. Abbott et al, Newton, Kansas., 1961-1963 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 1861. Docket No. 1832. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. Newton, Kansas., 1961-1963 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 1862. Docket No. 1833. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. Newton, Kansas., 1961-1963 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 1863. Docket No. 1844. RYA vs. Monon Railroad., 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 1864. Docket No. 1851. RYA vs. New York, Chicago and St. Louis Railroad Co. McCandless., 1962-1964 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Award No. 1865. Docket No. 1852. RYA vs. Minnesota Transfer Railway. Oliver., 1963 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Award No. 1866. Docket No. 1858. RYA vs. New York, Chicago and St. Louis Railroad. Miller., 1962-1964 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 1867. Docket No. 1688. RYA vs. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad., 1961-1964 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Award No. 1868. Docket No. 1689. RYA vs. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad. Holiday Pay., 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Award No. 1870. Docket No. 1905. Pennsylvania Railroad. Altoona, Pennsylvania., 1962-1964 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Award No. 1873. Docket No. 1781. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. Kovich and Hutchinson., 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Award No. 1874. Docket No. 1820. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway., 1961-1963 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Award No. 1877. Docket No. 1845. RYA vs. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad. Jones., 1962-1964 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 367-567 (Box 14)
  - Award No. 1238. Docket No. 1202. Chicago and North Western. EM Manrose Claim., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 1239. Docket No. 1204. Chicago and North Western. Neal Claim., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 1240. Docket No. 1205. Chicago and North Western. DD Nichols Claim., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 1241. Docket No. 1194. Chicago and North Western. PE Murphy Disqualification., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 1242. Docket No. 1190. Chicago and North Western. HC Oetell., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 1243. Docket No. 1206. Chicago and North Western. Claim., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 1244. Docket No. 1208. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie., 1956-1958 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 1245. Docket No. 1216. TRRA. WE Rollins., 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 2519. Chicago Great Western Railway Co., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Award No. 1246. Docket No. 1159. Chicago Great Western Railway Co. Reestablishment. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Contains notes in shorthand.
  - Award No. 1249. Docket No. 1160. Chicago Great Western. Claim of GE Carroll., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 1248. Docket No. 1161. Chicago Great Western. Claim of T, Guilfoyle., 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Award No. 1249. Docket No. 1162. Chicago Great Western. Claim of WE Schwader., 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Award No. 1250. Docket No. 1163. Chicago Great Western. Claim of ER Frank., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Award No. 1251. Docket No. 1164. Chicago Great Western. Claim of JC Bannon., 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Award No. 1252. Docket No. 1165. Chicago Great Western. Claim of JR Walsh for May 10-19 1949., 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Award No. 1253. Docket No. 1166. Chicago Great Western. Claim of UJ Sheffer of March 28 1949, et al., 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Award No. 1254. Docket No. 1167. Chicago Great Western. Claim of JA Barry for January 6 1950., 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Award No. 1255. Docket No. 1168. Chicago Great Western. Claim of ER Frank for March 3 1950., 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Award No. 1256. Docket No. 1169. Chicago Great Western. Claim of HG Meindl and CE Dougherty., 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Award No. 1259. Docket No. 1170. Chicago Great Western., 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Award No. 1258. Docket No. 1171. Chicago Great Western. Claim of EO McKliget for May 4 1954., 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Award No. 1259. Docket No. 1172. Chicago Great Western. Claim for ED Sheer for July 5 1955., 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Award No. 1271. Docket No. 1229. Chicago and Great Western. DE Dunaway Claim., 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    December 1956 - January 1957.
  - Award No. 1272. Docket No. 1230. Chicago and North Western. DE Janzen Claim for January 1 1957. (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Award No. 1273. Docket No. 1237. Chicago North Western., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Award No. 1274. Docket No. 1239. Pennsylvania Railroad. Yardmaster JT Melligan., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Award No. 1275. Docket No. 1248. Chicago and North Western. Disqualification., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Award No. 1276. Docket No. 1255. Spokane, Portland and Seattle. Time Claims and Positions Abolished Due to Strike., 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Award No. 1279. Docket No. 1294. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad. Claim for WA Earp. Oklahoma City., 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Award No. 1280. Docket No. 1306. Washington Terminal., 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Award No. 1282. Docket No. 1258. Union Pacific Railroad., 1956-1958 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Award No. 1284. Docket No. 1282. Delaware and Hudson Railroad. Payment in Lieu of Vacation. Deceased Yardmaster John P. Callahan., 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Award No. 1285. Docket No. 1283. Delaware and Hudson. Payment in Lieu of Vacation. Deceased Yardmaster James Hannon., 1958 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Award No. 1286. Docket No. 1285. The Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Co. Relief Yardmaster Work at Hazelwood Yard., 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Award No. 1287. Docket No. 1286. The Baltimore and Ohio Railroad CO. Remove Reprimand., 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 568-698 (Box 15)
  - Docket No. 788. Award No. 804. Pennsylvania Railroad. RJ Loreca., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Docket No. 790. Award No. 805. The Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Docket No. 792. Award No. 806. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. Argentine, Kansas., 1950-1952 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Docket No. 793. Award No. 807. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. Hathaway. Argentine, Kansas., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Docket No. 794. Award No. 808. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. Hathaway. Argentine, Kansas., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Docket No. 795. Award No. 809. Gulf, Colorado and Santa Fe Railway Co. Temple, Texas., 1954 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Docket No. 796. Award No. 810. The Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railway. Lowe. Argentine, Kansas., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 7)